bookmarkssite.info 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy - Bookmarkssite.info

At http://bookmarkssite.info we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by http://bookmarkssite.info and how we use it. 

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, http://bookmarkssite.info makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. 

Cookies and Web Beacons  
http://bookmarkssite.info uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site (such as Google AdSense advertisements). These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on http://bookmarkssite.info and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://bookmarkssite.info. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to http://bookmarkssite.info and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://bookmarkssite.info’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.   

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
